Guide to the Records of the Leake and Watts Children's Home 1802-1983 (bulk 1831-1949) MS 377
New-York Historical Society
- Series I - Leake and Watts Orphan House in the City of New York/Leake and Watts Children's Home, Inc., 1831-1983 (bulk 1831-1949)
  - Subseries I.3 - Administrative Records, 1816-1961
    - Early Legal Documents, 1816-1844 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence and Legal Documents, 1830-1839 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence and Legal Documents, 1840-1842 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence and Legal Documents, 1843-1845 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence and Legal Documents, 1846-1849 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence and Legal Documents, 1850-1854 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence and Legal Documents, 1855-1859 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 2)
    - By-Laws, 1857 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence and Legal Documents, 1860-1869 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence and Legal Documents, 1870-1889 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 5)
    - Booklet containing By-Laws, Charter, Trustee List, History, Addresses (2 copies), 1883 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence and Legal Documents, 1890-1897 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1901-1914 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 8)
    - Booklet containing By-Laws, Charter, Trustee List, History (4 copies), 1911 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1915 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1916 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1917-1919 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, circa 1920-1929 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Legal Documents, Memoranda, 1930-1939 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1940-1945 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence and Legal Documents, 1946 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1947-1949 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 8)
    - Administrative Correspondence and Memoranda - undated, circa 1876-1947 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 1)
    - Cemetery Certificates, Correspondence and Brochure, 1856-1945 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous School Memoranda and Correspondence, circa 1877-1934 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 3)
    - Menu and Meal Schedule 1911 and House Rules 1913, 1911, 1913 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 4)
    - Rules and Schedules, undated, circa 1914-1949 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 5)
    - Society for the Relief of Women and Children Correspondence, 1952-1961 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 6)
  - Subseries I.4 - Numbered files from the Office of William A. Kirk, circa 1918-1965
    William A. Kirk Esq. served as Clerk, later known as Secretary, of Leake and Watts, from [circa 1916-1955?]. He chaired the Real Estate Committee and handled legal matters. This subseries consists of files he maintained and grouped in the following order:
    I.4A - Mergers
    I.4B - Trusts, Wills and Bequests
    I.4C - Real Estate
    I.4D - Wards of Leake and Watts
    The files are arranged according to numbers Kirk assigned to each file, roughly chronologically. All original labels have been kept, although his non-archival folders have been replaced.
    - Subseries I.4A - Mergers
      - 2573 - Merger with Orphans Home and Asylum of the P.E.C. - Documents (folder 1 of 2), circa 1945-1947 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 6)
      - 2573 - Merger with Orphans Home and Asylum of the P.E.C. - Documents (folder 2 of 2), circa 1945-1947 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 7)
      - 2573-A - Merger with Orphans Home and Asylum of the P.E.C. - Merger Agareements, 1947 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 8)
      - 2573-A - Merger with Orphans Home and Asylum of the P.E.C. - Legal Documents, 1947-1953 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 1)
      - 2573-B - Merger with Orphans Home and Asylum of the P.E.C. - Extension of Powers, 1947-1953 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 2)
      - Merger with Orphans Home and Asylum of the P.E.C. - Report under Form 990, 1949 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 3)
      - 2737 - Merger with Sevilla-Hopewell, Early Proceedings, 1946-1950 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 4)
      - 2737A - Merger with Sevilla-Hopewell, Merger Papers including L&W By-laws 1947, 1947-1949 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 5)
      - 2737-B - Documents of Constituent Corporations incl. by-laws of Sevilla Home and will of Jose Sevilla, 1910, 1947-1949 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 1)
      - 2737-C - Merger with Sevilla-Hopewell - By-laws of New Corporation, 1949 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 2)
      - 2737-D - Merger with Sevilla-Hopewell - Certificate of Consolidation, 1949 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 3)
      - 2962 - Sale of Sevilla Land and Buildings, circa 1893-1906 and 1949-1950 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 4)
      - 3002 - Merger with Sevilla-Hopewell - Organization Meeting and Correspondence, 1947-1949 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 1)
      - 3052 - Merger with Sevilla-Hopewell - Summerland Property Documents, 1949 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 2)
    - Subseries I.4B - Trusts, Wills and Bequests
      - 948 - Agreement between Edwin Gould, Edwin Gould Foundation, and Trustees of Leake and Watts, 1921-1931 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 3)
      - 3982 - Accountings by Bankers Trust Company on the Edwin Gould Trusts, 1932-1956 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 4)
      - 972-C - Estate of Willard H. Jones - Minnie Myerson Trust, 1938-1943 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 5)
      - 1705 - Estate of Melville S. Page, 1938-1942 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 6)
      - 1720 - Estates of Mary J. Tompkins, Thaddeus C. Tompkins, 1937-1942 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 7)
      - 1768 - Estate of Joseph Wiener, 1938 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 1)
      - 1868 - Estate of J.G.B. Waring, 1934-1939 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 2)
      - 1901 - Estate of Katharine L. Mather, 1939-1949 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 3)
      - 2024 - Estate of Abraham Finelite, 1942-1953 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 4)
      - 2043 - Estate of Mary Curtis Martin, 1941 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 5)
      - 2077 - Estate of Cora Ros, 1941 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 6)
      - 2185 - Estate of Harry M. Clancy, 1942-1951 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 7)
      - 2203 - Estate of William R. Hobson, 1942 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 8)
      - 2204 - Estate of Isabella Hughes, Rent Schedules, 1942 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 9)
      - 2246 - Estate of Robert Peele, 1942-1944 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 10)
      - 2271 - Estate of Laura M. Elliot, 1943 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 11)
      - 2307 - Estate of Hugh M. Anderson, 1944-1946 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 12)
      - 2339 - Estate of Sophie Mackay, 1944 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 13)
      - 2615 - Estate of Marie MacLean, 1946 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 14)
      - 2668 - Estate of David C. Bacon, 1947-1948 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 15)
      - 2700 - Estate of Raymond V. Carpenter, 1947-1948 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 16)
      - 2719 - Estate of Inez Irene duBois, 1947 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 17)
      - 2775 - Estate of Grace B. Selfridge, 1947 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 18)
      - 2787 - Estate of Emily Dater, 1947 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 19)
      - 2797 - Estate of Asa Thompson, 1945 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 20)
      - 2830 - Estate of Berta M. Bache, 1948 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 21)
      - 2845 - Estate of John J. Watts, 1945-1948 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 22)
      - 2937 - Estate of Anna Selden, 1948 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 23)
    - Subseries I.4C - Real Estate
      - 734 - Property in Bronx, Cancellation of Taxes, 1918-1931 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 1)
      - 1129 - Leake and Watts vs. 19 First Avenue Inc., 1932-1937 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 2)
      - 1250 - Harry F. Johnson papers before commencement of action, 1931-1934 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 3)
      - 1250-A - Harry F. Johnson papers after commencement of action (folder 1 of 2), 1934-1941 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 4)
      - 1250-A - Harry F. Johnson papers after commencement of action (folder 2 of 2), 1934-1941 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 5)
      - 1250-B - Leake and Watts vs. Harry F. Johnson - probate of will of Mary H. Johnson, 1937-1938 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 6)
      - 1250-C - Harry F. Johnson - papers re: purchase of title by 264-266 First Ave. Corp., 1937-1938 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 7)
      - 1419-A - 264-266 First Avenue Corp. Rehabilitation of Property, 1936-1939 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 8)
      - 1488 - Leake and Watts Realty Corp. (folder 1 of 2), 1935-1948 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 9)
      - 1488 - Leake and Watts Realty Corp. (folder 2 of 2), 1935-1948 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 10)
      - 1495 - Brindsley Realty Co., 1935-1947 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 11)
      - 1609 - 870 Sixth Avenue Subway Construction, 1936-1941 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 12)
      - 1614 - Leake and Watts Realty Corp. Financial and Income Tax Reports, 1936-1945 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 1)
      - 1624 - Removal of Violations of Multiple Dwelling Law - 21-23 First Ave., 1937-1940 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 2)
      - 1636 - Sale of 233 Division St. and 244 E. Broadway, 1936-1940 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 3)
      - 1682 - Removal of Violations of Multiple Dwelling Law - Tenement House Blanks, 1937 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 4)
      - 1702 - Rehabilitation of 53-55 Stanton St., 1937-1939 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 5)
      - 1702-A - Rehabiliation of 53-55 Stanton St., 1937-1938 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 6)
      - 1710 - Sale of 53-55 Stanton St., 1937 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 7)
      - 1960 - Property Tax Appeals, 1940-1943 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 8)
      - 1960 A and B - Property Tax Appeals, 1943-1946 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 9)
      - 1960-C - Property Tax Appeals, 1945-1947 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 10)
      - 2084 - 870 Sixth Avenue - Assessment re: Sixth Avenue El, 1941-1944 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 11)
      - 2142 - Leake and Watts Realty Corp. - Objections to garage on 34th St., 1941-1947 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 12)
      - 2189 - Exemption of Lots 130 and 65 in Block 3428 in the Bronx, 1942-1944 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 13)
      - 2198 - Tax Exemption, 1941-1942 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 14)
      - 2200 - Income Tax Exemption Form 990 and Form 1023, 1937-1944 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 15)
      - 2238 - Leake and Watts Realty Corp. Dissolution, 1936-1945 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 1)
      - 2242 - Lease of 138-140 W. 54th St., 1942-1946 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 2)
      - 2242-A - Leake and Watts vs. Fergus Motors rent dispute 138-140 W. 54th St., 1944-1946 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 3)
      - 2528 - Proposed sale of 138-140 W. 54th St., 1945-1946 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 4)
      - 2535 - Rent Statements 56-58 Roosevelt St., 1940 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 5)
      - 2535 - Rent Statements 56-58 Roosevelt St., 1941 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 6)
      - 2535 - Rent Statements 56-58 Roosevelt St., 1942 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 7)
      - 2535 - Rent Statements 56-58 Roosevelt St., 1943 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 8)
      - 2535 - Rent Statements 56-58 Roosevelt St., 1944 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 9)
      - 2535 - Rent Statements 56-58 Roosevelt St., 1945 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 10)
      - 2535 - Rent Statements 56-58 Roosevelt St., 1946 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 11)
      - 2551 - 264-266 First Ave. Corp - Zoning Ordinance 870 Sixth Ave., 1946 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 12)
      - 2577 - Mortgage on 333-5 E. 55th St., 1946-1947 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 13)
      - 2606-A - Street widening matter, 1948 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 14)
      - 2657 - Sale of 870 Sixth Ave., 1946-1950 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 15)
      - 2742 - Mortgage on 1153 Colgate Ave., Bronx, 1938-1947 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 16)
      - 2745 - Mulock Memorial, Mortgage, 6312 Bay Parkway, Brooklyn, 1947-1955 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 17)
      - 2746 - Orphans Fund, Mortgage, 1 Raleigh Place, Brooklyn, 1947-1954 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 18)
      - 2748 - Orphans Fund, Mortgage, 228 New Lots Ave., Brooklyn, 1947-1949 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 19)
      - 2767 - Mortgage, 182 Hastings St., Brooklyn, 1931-1947 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 20)
      - 2768 - Mortgage, 1243 Avenue U, Brooklyn, 1947 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 21)
      - 2770 - 240 East 47th Street, 1937-1947 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 22)
      - 2781 - Mortgage, 216 E. 114th St., 1948-1950 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 23)
      - 2788 - 21 First Ave. lawsuit, 1947-1948 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 24)
      - 2791 - 50 Howard Ave., Brooklyn, 1947-1948 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 25)
      - 2796 - Tax Exemptions, 1947-1965 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 26)
      - 2876 - 50 Howard Ave. Tax Protest, 1948-1949 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 1)
      - 2880 - 21-23 First Ave. violation, 1948 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 2)
      - 2882 - 1948-1949 Tax Protests - various premises, 1946-1949 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 3)
      - 2889 - Rent Hardship Cases, 1942-1953 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 4)
      - 2894 - 1630 E. 15th St., Brooklyn, 1948 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 5)
      - 2912 - 195 Sutter Ave., Brooklyn, 1953 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 6)
      - 2914 - 110-26 169th St., Jamaica N.Y., 1944-1953 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 7)
      - 2918 - Tax Exemption - Yonkers Property, 1948-1953 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 8)
      - 2926 - Proposed sale of property to Sisters of Charity, 1948 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 9)
      - 2927 - 384 North Ave., New Rochelle, 1948-1949 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 10)
      - 2960 - 837 First Ave. - Widening of East 47th St., 1948-1950 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 11)
      - 2959 - Fire at Yonkers October 9, 1948 [includes photographic prints], 1948-1950 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 12)
      - 2981 - Second Fire, November 29, 1948, 1948-1949 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 13)
      - 2989 - Contract with Lincoln Wrecking Co., 1948-1949 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 14)
      - 3008 - Manhattan real estate valuation case, 1947-1949 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 15)
      - 3026 - Garden City Lots, 1949-1950 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 16)
      - 3071 - 2846 Stillwell Ave., Brooklyn, Mortgage, 1949 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 17)
      - 3125 - 870 Sixth Ave. petition for rent increase, 1948-1951 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 18)
    - Subseries I.4D - Wards of Leake and Watts
      - 935 - Alexander Takacs, circa 1930-1940 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 19)
      - 1090 - Alexander Carlson, 1927-1932 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 20)
      - 1153 - Charles Bentz, 1903-1933 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 21)
      - 2854 - Donald Hoetger, 1948 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 22)
  - Subseries I.5 - Financial Records, 1833-1957
    The subseries contains 119 account books, grouped together by type, and arranged chronologically within each type. The volumes are followed by 2 folders of miscellaneous financial documents.
    - Treasurer's Accounts with the Board of Trustees, 1833-1842 (Offsite-box LW-9, Volume 44)
    - Treasurer's Accounts with the Board of Trustees, 1842-1863 (Offsite-box LW-9A, Volume 45)
    - Treasurer's Accounts with the Board of Trustees, 1863-1892 (Offsite-box LW-9, Volume 46)
    - Trustees' Accounts, 1863-1881 (Offsite-box LW-9, Volume 47)
    - Trustees' Accounts, 1881-1892 (Offsite-box LW-9, Volume 48)
    - Trustees' Accounts, 1893-1913 (Offsite-box LW-10, Volume 49)
    - Treasurer's Receipt Book, 1871-1892 (Offsite-box LW-10, Volume 50)
    - Treasurer's Receipt Book, 1892-1900 (Offsite-box LW-10, Volume 51)
    - Expenses, 1866-1876 (Offsite-box LW-10, Volume 52)
    - Expenses, 1898-1899 (Offsite-box LW-10, Volume 53)
    - Expenses, 1898-1900 (Offsite-box LW-11, Volume 54)
    - Expenses (Day Book), 1900-1902 (Offsite-box LW-11, Volume 55)
    - Expenses, 1904-1913 (Offsite-box LW-11, Volume 56)
    - Expense Ledger, 1905-1914 (Offsite-box LW-11, Volume 57)
    - Expense Ledger, 1909-1912 (Offsite-box LW-11, Volume 58)
    - Expense Ledger, 1910-1913 (Offsite-box LW-11, Volume 59)
    - Expense Ledger, 1913-1914 (Offsite-box LW-12, Volume 60)
    - Expense Ledger, 1914-1920 (Offsite-box LW-12, Volume 61)
    - Register of Expenses (Oversize), 1916-1917 (Offsite-box LW-50, Volume 62)
    - Register of Expenses (Oversize), 1916-1920 (Offsite-box LW-50, Volume 63)
    - Register of Expenses (Oversize), 1920-1924 (Offsite-box LW-50, Volume 64)
    - Register of Expenses (Oversize), 1924-1927 (Offsite-box LW-51, Volume 65)
    - Register of Expenses (Oversize), 1927-1930 (Offsite-box LW-51, Volume 66)
    - Register of Expenses (Oversize), 1930-1933 (Offsite-box LW-51, Volume 67)
    - Register of Expenses (Oversize), 1933-1936 (Offsite-box LW-52, Volume 68)
    - Register of Expenses (Oversize), 1936-1938 (Offsite-box LW-52, Volume 69)
    - Register of Expenses (Oversize), 1938-1941 (Offsite-box LW-52, Volume 70)
    - Ledger, 1930-1931 (Offsite-box LW-12, Volume 71)
    - Ledger, 1933 (Offsite-box LW-12, Volume 72)
    - Ledger, 1934 (Offsite-box LW-12, Volume 73)
    - Ledger, 1935 (Offsite-box LW-13, Volume 74)
    - Ledger, 1936 (Offsite-box LW-13, Volume 75)
    - Ledger, 1937 (Offsite-box LW-13, Volume 76)
    - Ledger, 1938 (Offsite-box LW-13, Volume 77)
    - Ledger, 1939 (Offsite-box LW-13, Volume 78)
    - Ledger, 1940 (Offsite-box LW-13, Volume 79)
    - Ledger, 1941 (Offsite-box LW-13, Volume 80)
    - Ledger, 1942 (Offsite-box LW-14, Volume 81)
    - Ledger, 1943 (Offsite-box LW-14, Volume 82)
    - Ledger, 1944-1945 (Offsite-box LW-14, Volume 83)
    - General Ledger Trial Balance, 1920-1924 (Offsite-box LW-14, Volume 84)
    - General Ledger Trial Balance, 1925-1935 (Offsite-box LW-14, Volume 85)
    - General Ledger Trial Balance, 1930-1937 (Offsite-box LW-19, Volume 86)
    - General Ledger Trial Balance, 1937-1941 (Offsite-box LW-19, Volume 87)
    - General Ledger Trial Balance, 1941-1948 (Offsite-box LW-19, Volume 88)
    - Cash Account Book, 1893-1901 (Offsite-box LW-15, Volume 89)
    - Cash Account Book, 1901-1904 (Offsite-box LW-15, Volume 90)
    - Cash Account Book, 1905-1909 (Offsite-box LW-15, Volume 91)
    - Cash Account Book, 1909-1912 (Offsite-box LW-15, Volume 92)
    - Cash Account Book, 1912-1915 (Offsite-box LW-15, Volume 93)
    - Cash Account Book, 1915-1919 (Offsite-box LW-16, Volume 94)
    - Cash Account Book, 1919-1925 (Offsite-box LW-16, Volume 95)
    - Ledger, 1914-1915 (Offsite-box LW-16, Volume 96)
    - Ledger, 1915 (Offsite-box LW-19, Volume 97)
    - Ledger, 1927 (Offsite-box LW-16, Volume 98)
    - Ledger, 1930-1934 (Offsite-box LW-16, Volume 99)
    - Ledger, 1934-1940 (Offsite-box LW-16, Volume 100)
    - Ledger - General Fund, 1941-1952 (Offsite-box LW-16, Volume 101)
    - Ledger - Special Fund, 1938-1951 (Offsite-box LW-16, Volume 102)
    - Journal, 1914-1925 (Offsite-box LW-17, Volume 103)
    - Journal, 1925-1928 (Offsite-box LW-17, Volume 104)
    - Journal, 1928-1933 (Offsite-box LW-17, Volume 105)
    - Journal, 1933-1938 (Offsite-box LW-17, Volume 106)
    - Journal, 1939-1944 (Offsite-box LW-17, Volume 107)
    - Journal, 1944-1949 (Offsite-box LW-17, Volume 108)
    - Superintendent's Receipt Book, 1877-1880 (Offsite-box LW-17, Volume 109)
    - Superintendent's Receipt Book, 1892-1898 (Offsite-box LW-17, Volume 110)
    - Superintendent's Receipt Book, 1898-1901 (Offsite-box LW-18, Volume 111)
    - Superintendent's Receipt Book, 1902-1904 (Offsite-box LW-18, Volume 112)
    - Superintendent's Receipt Book, 1904-1906 (Offsite-box LW-18, Volume 113)
    - Salary Receipt Book, 1878-1879 (Offsite-box LW-18, Volume 114)
    - Salary Receipt Book, 1879-1882 (Offsite-box LW-18, Volume 115)
    - Salary Receipt Book, 1926 (Offsite-box LW-18, Volume 116)
    - Superintendent's Accounts, 1941-1947 (Offsite-box LW-18, Volume 117)
    - Cash Book, 1941-1947 (Offsite-box LW-18, Volume 118)
    - Petty Cash, 1941-1943 (Offsite-box LW-18, Volume 119)
    - Petty Cash, 1943-1945 (Offsite-box LW-19, Volume 120)
    - Petty Cash, 1945-1947 (Offsite-box LW-19, Volume 121)
    - Home School Operating Ledger (Oversize), 1928-1930 (Offsite-box LW-58, Volume 122)
    - Home School Special Accounts, 1939-1945 (Offsite-box LW-19, Volume 123)
    - Tivoli Farm Ledger, 1940-1947 (Offsite-box LW-20, Volume 123A)
    - Cash Receipts - Children's Accounts, 1915-1923 (Offsite-box LW-20, Volume 124)
    - Cash Receipts - Children's Accounts, 1923-1925 (Offsite-box LW-20, Volume 125)
    - Cash Receipts - Children's Accounts, 1927-1929 (Offsite-box LW-20, Volume 126)
    - Cash Receipts - Children's Accounts, 1930-1935 (Offsite-box LW-20, Volume 127)
    - Cash Receipts - Children's Accounts, 1935-1942 (Offsite-box LW-20, Volume 128)
    - Cash Receipts - Children's Accounts, 1942-1949 (Offsite-box LW-20, Volume 129)
    - Children's Board Accounts, 1914-1922 (Offsite-box LW-20, Volume 130)
    - Children's Board Accounts, 1922-1926 (Offsite-box LW-20, Volume 131)
    - Children's Board Accounts, 1927-1928 (Offsite-box LW-21, Volume 132)
    - Children's Board Accounts, 1928-1929 (Offsite-box LW-21, Volume 133)
    - Children's Board Accounts, 1930-1931 (Offsite-box LW-21, Volume 134)
    - Children's Board Accounts, 1932-1933 (Offsite-box LW-21, Volume 135)
    - Children's Board Accounts, 1934-1937 (Offsite-box LW-21, Volume 136)
    - Children's Board Accounts, 1937-1943 (Offsite-box LW-21, Volume 137)
    - Children's Board Accounts, 1943-1949 (Offsite-box LW-21, Volume 138)
    - Index of Board Accounts, 1928-1929 (Offsite-box LW-21, Volume 139)
    - Index of Board Accounts, 1932-1935 (Offsite-box LW-21, Volume 140)
    - Children's Accounts by N.Y. County, 1926-1927 (Offsite-box LW-22, Volume 141)
    - Payments for Children - Edwin Gould Foundation, 1924-1928 (Offsite-box LW-22, Volume 142)
    - Payments for Children - Edwin Gould Foundation, 1929-1932 (Offsite-box LW-22, Volume 143)
    - Check Stubs for College Expenses - Peck Fund, 1934-1938 (Offsite-box LW-22, Volume 144)
    - Check Stubs for College Expenses - Peck Fund, 1938-1943 (Offsite-box LW-22, Volume 145)
    - Expenditures and Bank Withdrawals (Oversize), 1925-1938 (Offsite-box LW-53, Volume 146)
    - Receipts and Bank Deposits (Oversize), 1925-1933 (Offsite-box LW-53, Volume 147)
    - Receipts and Bank Deposits (Oversize), 1934-1942 (Offsite-box LW-53, Volume 148)
    - Bank Accounts (Oversize), 1942-1949 (Offsite-box LW-54, Volume 149)
    - Check Stubs (Oversize), 1907-1909 (Offsite-box LW-53, Volume 150)
    - Check Stubs (Oversize), 1912-1914 (Offsite-box LW-53, Volume 151)
    - Check Stubs (Oversize), 1926-1927 (Offsite-box LW-54, Volume 151A)
    - Inventory of Assets and De Peyster Fund Donations, 1912 (Offsite-box LW-22, Volume 152)
    - Subsidiary Ledger - Investments and Accounts Receivable, 1925-1935 (Offsite-box LW-22, Volume 153)
    - Special Donations Ledger, 1926-1933 (Offsite-box LW-22, Volume 154)
    - Appeal Accounts, 1931-1937 (Offsite-box LW-22, Volume 155)
    - Appeal Account Book, 1935-1940 (Offsite-box LW-23, Volume 156)
    - Appeal Account Book, 1940-1946 (Offsite-box LW-23, Volume 157)
    - Appeal Account Book, 1946-1957 (Offsite-box LW-23, Volume 158)
    - Accounts - Various, 1925-1926 (Offsite-box LW-23, Volume 159)
    - Accounts, 1938-1950 (Offsite-box LW-26, Volume 159A)
    - Special Accounts Book, 1955-1962 (Offsite-box LW-23, Volume 159B)
    - St. Christopher's Chapel Donations and Expenses, 1942-1946 (Offsite-box LW-23, Volume 160)
    - Binder of Accounts Alphabetical M-Z, circa 1946-1951 (Offsite-box LW-22A, Volume 161)
    - Miscellaneous Financial Documents, circa 1907-1932 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 23)
    - Check book, bank book, cancelled checks, 1911-1959 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 24)
  - Subseries I.6 - Records of Children, Clubs, Activities and Alumni, 1843-1964
    Scope and content
    The subseries consists of 25 volumes and 2 boxes of documents related to children and their lives and activities at the Leake and Watts Orphan House/Leake and Watts Children's Home, and records of the alumni association, the Leake and Watts Association. Materials include admissions registers, documents recording the names of children at the home, infirmary records, records of visitors to the home including visitors to children and visits of returning alumni recorded in the same volume, records of the alumni association, and, at the end of the subseries, records of other clubs and activities. Volumes are arranged first, followed by documents in boxes.